Speaker: Hannah met Jamie last summer.
It was Hannah’s birthday and she and her friends went to a club.
They wanted to dance, but they didn’t like the music, so Hannah went to speak to the DJ.
‘This music is awful,’ she said.
‘Could you play something else?’
The DJ looked at her and said, ‘Don’t worry, I have the perfect song for you.’
Two minutes later, he said, ‘The next song is by Pink.
It’s called ‘Get the Party Started’
and it’s for a beautiful girl over there who’s wearing a pink dress.’
Hannah knew that the song was for her.
When Hannah and her friends left the club, the DJ was waiting for her at the door.
‘Hi, I’m Jamie,’ he said to Hannah.
‘Can I see you again?’
So Hannah gave him her phone number.
The next day, Jamie phoned Hannah and invited her to dinner.
He took her to a very romantic French restaurant and they talked all evening.
Although the food wasn’t very good, they had a wonderful time.
After that, Jamie and Hannah saw each other every day.
Every evening, when Hannah finished work, they met at 5.30 in a coffee bar in the high street.
They were madly in love.
One evening in October, Hannah was at work.
As usual, she was going to meet Jamie at 5.30.
It was dark and it was raining.
She looked at her watch.
It was 5.20! She was going to be late!
She ran to her car and got in.
At 5.25 she was driving along the high street.
She was going very fast because she was in a hurry.
Suddenly, a man ran across the road.
He was wearing a dark coat, so Hannah didn’t see him at first.
Quickly, she put her foot on the brake…